{
    "subject": "resource/VIS_Entertainment",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Companies_of_Scotland",
    "human_readable": "The subject of VIS Entertainment is Category:Companies_of_Scotland.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9503623247146606,
            "question": "Is VIS Entertainment a company based in Scotland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8550084829330444,
            "question": "Are there any well-known companies in Scotland that are not from the same category as VIS Entertainment?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7203009724617004,
            "question": "What category does VIS Entertainment belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6727204918861389,
            "question": "How does VIS Entertainment contribute to the Scottish economy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6694076061248779,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of successful companies from various categories in Scotland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6455411911010742,
            "question": "Can you name some other companies from the same category as VIS Entertainment?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5673693418502808,
            "question": "What are some of the key industries present in Scotland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5559321045875549,
            "question": "What type of business does VIS Entertainment operate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3659757673740387,
            "question": "Does VIS Entertainment have any subsidiaries or branches in other countries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26797598600387573,
            "question": "What is the geographical location of VIS Entertainment's operations?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of VIS Entertainment is Category:Companies_of_Scotland.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4548_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does VIS Entertainment have any subsidiaries or branches in other countries?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4548_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of business does VIS Entertainment operate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4548_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the key industries present in Scotland?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4548_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4548_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4548_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4548_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4548_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4548_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4548_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4548_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4548_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4548_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4548_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about VIS Entertainment being a game design and development company located in Scotland, which supports the statement that it belongs to the category of companies of Scotland."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The subject of VIS Entertainment is based out of Scotland but not exclusively a company of Scotland, as indicated by the phrase \"Companies_of_Scotland\" which implies an exclusive category. However, the correct categorization would be more general, such as \"Scottish companies\", \"Companies based in Scotland\", or simply \"Video game developers based in Scotland\".",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}